With those born with natural talents, it feels as if they excel without really trying.
那些生来就有天赋的人，给人的感觉是，他们好像不怎么费力就能出类拔萃。
But what about those of us who don’t have a natural talent?
可是，我们当中那些没有天赋的人又当如何呢？
We’ve been told all our lives that if you work hard, you too can succeed.
我们从小到大一直听人说：只要你努力，你也能成功。
But with the release of Angela Duckworth’s Grit, we are given a new key to success.
但随着安杰拉·达克沃思的《坚毅》一书出版，我们得到了一把通往成功的新钥匙。
“As much as talent counts, effort counts twice,” says Duckworth in Grit.
“天赋固然重要，但努力的分量是它的两倍，”达克沃思在《坚毅》中说。
She introduces a new concept that talent may be overrated, and if you want real success, what you need is grit, the perfect combination of passion and persistence.
她提出了一个新观念：天赋可能被高估了；如果你想获得真正的成功，你需要的是坚毅，即激情与坚持的完美结合。
Even if you have natural talent, it’s nothing without grit.
即使你有天赋，没有坚毅，天赋也算不了什么。
Duckworth says grit is the difference between success and failure.
达克沃思说，成功与失败的差别就在于坚毅。
A person who has grit is more likely to succeed than a person who does not.
有坚毅品质的人比没有这种品质的人更有可能成功。
When we think about attaining success—whether it’s landing that job or learning that new skill—our thoughts are immediately burdened by all the things we must first learn.
每当我们想到要取得成功——无论是拿下那份工作，还是学会那项新技能——我们的思绪立刻就会被所有必须先学会的东西所累。
If you want that new job, you have to learn the job skills, then the interview skills, then how to dress the part—and you must be perfect at all of them.
如果你想得到那份新工作，就得学会工作技能，然后是面试技能，再然后是如何穿着得体、符合身份——而且每一项你都必须做到完美。
Grit is different because it tells us that perfection isn’t the goal.
坚毅之所以不同，是因为它告诉我们，完美并不是目标。
Grit lifts the unreasonable expectations off our shoulders.
坚毅卸下了压在我们肩上的不合理期望。
Grit tells us that the door is open wider than we first thought possible.
坚毅告诉我们，那扇门开得比我们起初想象的还要大。
Grit allows us to redefine our goals.
坚毅让我们得以重新定义自己的目标。
Think about it: what’s something you’ve always wanted to do, but gave up because you “don’t have the skills for it”?
想一想：有没有哪件事你一直想做，却因为自己“不具备做这件事的技能”而放弃了？
What’s something you love but aren’t good at?
又有什么事是你热爱、却并不擅长的？
The real workings of grit are to have sustainable passion and continue to try.
坚毅真正起作用的方式，在于保持持久的激情，并不断尝试。
Effort means more than your natural ability.
努力比你天生的能力更重要。
Even if you haven’t mastered a skill, grit tells you that you can still succeed if you can transform your passion into action.
坚毅告诉你：即使你还没有掌握某项技能，只要能把激情转化为行动，你仍然可以成功。
In a way, Duckworth is giving new hope to people who have shut the doors on their dreams.
从某种意义上说，达克沃思正在给那些已经对自己的梦想关上大门的人带来新的希望。
She is saying it is possible that you can accomplish anything.
她是在说，你做成任何事都是有可能的。
If at first you fail, then try one more time with grit.
如果一开始失败了，那就凭着坚毅再试一次。